[{"answer": "I'm interested in what happened.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's an interview people are still talking about.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What the hell are you doing?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't think I really do have any conflict with them in the sense that -- that that guy you're talking about, that photographer, I mean, I think the most important thing to remember is I did not punch the guy.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Why do you have such conflict with them?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "You have a very different opinion than I do.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "I would call them a tax, it's a tax on show business, isn't it?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "If I could press a button tomorrow and flush them all down some swirling sewer vortex, I would do it.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, that's not really practical.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "But you can never have any more publicity in any newspaper or magazine for anything you do?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Any names?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, Russell Crowe is extremely prepared.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "But who are the ones you look at and go, that's where I want to be?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I'd have to say -- and this is true of a lot of comedians, and I've talked to other comedians and heard them say the same thing.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "When you wanted to get into show business, was part of the allure of it being famous, if you're honest, when you look back to that time?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, first let me just back up a little bit and say, I don't have to live in the real world, I'm a fiction writer.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "If you were running a news network, what would you do?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Well, you know the answer to that, don't you?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "A bit awkward?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Holy cow.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Who is the biggest most romantic sexual singer you've ever deployed?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Has to be.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Has to be, right?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "You know what, I always like to make the guest feel like they're the star.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Were you really trying?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "You know, contrary to public perception.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Something like that.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "You've already sold, what, 10 million albums?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "I don't even want to say it.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "What's the worst song you've ever written?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "And I -- because -- well, I can explain all that.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Literally.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Literally?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I have my favorite records.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What is the song of all the songs that you've ever been involved with -- what is the one, if I said, right, Glen, you've got five minute to live, you can play one song to be remembered by, the defining song?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I loved \"One of These Nights.\"", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "What's your -- what's your number one?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I love Adele.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "And who of all the acts out there now, who's the one that excites you, the modern crowd?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Yes, go ahead.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Can I touch it?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "ATSON: It feels nice.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "How does it feel?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "It's overwhelming.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "How does it really feel to be Bubba Watson right now?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "That is genuinely why, isn't it?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, I don't put myself in those situations.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "How do you feel now?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "When was the last time you hit a man?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Good shot?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Well, when you're out there, you have to take the winning -- winner's attitude, as I do, and I can't go out there thinking I'm feeling sorry because they're trying to win, too.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "You're in the zone and you're winning, what do you experience?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Well, it's just hard work.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Not just any old champion, to be a great champion?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "It's everything.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Is it all of it, Usain?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "If you want to show me the door, that's fine, too.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "No, I remember it quite well.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you remember the night that she died well, or is it now something you've blocked out of your head?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I'm interested in what happened.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Let me help you.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "What the hell are you doing?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "-- on your story.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Now you want to know what happened that night?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I'm curious about --", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "So far.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Am I right so far?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I think you're here because you've written a book about your life.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "No, but your questions are boring, because -- I mean, even what you just said, are you sure the people at Tibet give a (EXPLETIVE DELETED) about any of this?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I didn't murder my wife.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Than the murder of your wife?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I cannot speak for Maria.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Do you think there is a good chance you can get back together?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I would say that it makes no difference.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Was it more that?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "The big white elephant in the room we can't avoid.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "How are you handling it?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Did you ever touch a beaver?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Well, it's all of the above and a whole lot more.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Well, if not him, somebody else.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Would she have ever gone down that route, do you think, without Bobby Brown in her life?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I think that we all as artists, because we're highly sensitive people.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Do you think she had that tendency anyway?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Because you supplied the plane, didn't you?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Amazing.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "He was a great generalist.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "What was the secret ingredient that he had?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "I read the first seven chapters.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Have you read \"Fifty Shades of Grey\"?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Was there anything in there you hadn't already done yourself?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I know you probably imagined differently and have several nights during the week when you go to bed.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "You surprise me.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "No manacles?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "It's unreadable.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Did you read the entire trilogy?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "Just out of pure curiosity.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "Why would you read that?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "qSentId": 779}, {"answer": "Not much at all.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 808, "question": "Hollywood smiley?", "qSentId": 807}, {"answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 820, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "qSentId": 819}, {"answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "Cut that.", "docId": "121225pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 849}]